# **FAZRIAL FEIZAL**

South of Tangerang, Banten | +6285311229339 | it.fazrial@hotmail.com | bit.ly/fazrial

### SUMMARY

I am an Informatics Engineering student at the National Institute of Science and Technology Jakarta who loves and interests in Technology, Data, and Business. Now, I am pursuing Data Analyst Career path. I was experienced to manage a small team in sort of volunteering event, hardware-network troubleshooting, and made a small insight.

# **WORKING EXPERIENCE**

### PT PLN (Persero) UIT JBB UPT Pulogadung - IT Support Internship

April 2021 – May 2021 (2 Months)

Jakarta

- Responsibility about function of network hardware
- Maintaning and configuring the network problem
- Designing the new network system

### VOLUNTERING EXPERIENCE

### Indonesia Millennial Connect - Event Planner at Aksi Sahabat Desa's Event

November 2020 - March 2021 (5 Months)

Jakarta

- Achieved The Best Committee for Event Planner Affairs
- Concepting the pre-main event
- Concepting the sub event such as a special day or big day
- Managing operator as a sub team

### Indonesia Millennial Connect – Operator at Eco Talks IMC x Lokalate

July 2020 – August 2020 (2 Months)

Jakarta

- Operating the webinar session
- Responsible for the webinar sessions
- Creating webinar session procedure and concept

# Indonesia Millennial Connect – PIC of Operator Division

May 2020 – July 2020 (3 Months)

Jakarta

- Achieved The Best Crew Festival Indonesia Bangkit
- Mentoring the next-gen of operator
- Responsible for the webinar sessions
- Creating webinar session procedure and concept
- Mentoring the next-gen of operator
- Attended speakers by Najwa Shihab, Sandiaga Uno, Seto Mulyadi, Hendy Setiono etc

### **EDUCATION**

# National Institute of Science and Technology, Jakarta Informatics Engineering / 3.81 out of 4.00

2018 - 2022 (Predicted)

Machine Learning Course: Made a brand prediction using KNN Classifier

## SOFT SKILLS

- Analytical Skill
- Management Skill
- Critical Thinking

### HARD SKILLS

- Python (Programming Language, Visualization Tools)
- PowerBI (Data Visualization Software)
- MySQL Workbench (SQL Database)
- Figma (UI Design)
- Microsoft Office (Word, PowerPoint, Excel)
- Basic Cisco Switch and Router Configuring

# LANGUAGE

- Bahasa Indonesia (Native)
- English (Intermediate)

### COURSE COMPLETIONS

### Indonesia AI - Intermediate Python

AIM07062021411 | 2021

- Learn NumPy, Pandas and Matplotlib Library
- Learn Data Visualization (Visualizing The Most Visitor, Composition of Reservation Status, etc)
- Learn Data Analysis (Hotel Reservation Analysis)

### Sanbercode – Python Data Science

19389/84/BDG/P-SNBR/CODE/2021 | 2021

- Learn NumPy, Pandas and Matplotlib Library
- Learn Data Visualization (Visualizing Price Over Phone Feature, Feature Comparison Over Brand, etc)
- Learn Basic Machine Learning (Phone Price Classifier)

### Monash University Coursera – Excel Skills for Business : Essentials

VG6X8R78X96M | 2021

- Learn Excel Tools
- Learn Basic Data Handling (Filtering, Sorting and Replacing)
- Learn Data Visualization (Visualizing Sales History)